Andrew Vaccaro

Software Engineer

Experienced full stack developer with a strong focus on WordPress development. Proficient in PHP, Vue, JavaScript, and CSS with extensive experience working closely with in-house designers and marketers to build fully custom themes and plugins using a modern development workflow.

EXPERIENCE

IT Programmer at Unicell (2023 - present)

 Develop and maintain features for a Laravel-based internal web application to streamline inventory management, invoicing, reporting, and IT support ticketing.

Software Engineer at Cypress North (2016 - 2023)

- Work closely with in-house design and marketing team members to create pixel-perfect
 WordPress themes that adhere to SEO best practices using a modern workflow consisting of AlpineJS, TailwindCSS, and Composer.
- Customize and integrate WooCommerce storefront into WordPress site utilizing custom fields and taxonomies to enhance shopping experience and sales.
- Create custom store locator maps using Google Maps API that are fully populated, editable, and filterable using custom post types and taxonomies.
- Design, develop, and maintain an ASP.NET Core application that automates renter background checks for landlords using Transunion's credit report API and Stripe, resulting in \$1M+ yearly revenue.
- Create engaging user experiences to drive website traffic through the development of landing pages using parallax scrolling effects and SVG/CSS animations.
- Develop a Vue touchscreen kiosk application for trade shows to display product information with offline content editing capabilities.

Freelancer (2022 - present)

• Design, create, maintain and host custom WordPress websites.

EDUCATION

Rochester Institute of Technology (2012 - 2016)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

SKILLS

WordPress

WooCommerce

Laravel

TailwindCSS

PHP

JavaScript

Vue

• Advanced Custom Fields

.NET Core

Webpack

Photoshop/Figma/XD

Git